<?xml version="1.0"?>
<contentList xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <content contentuid="hb9eea705g761ag438fg9ec6g23a9e2a8d1c5" version="53">Listen. Think. What does the drow miss most about the Underdark?</content>
  <content contentuid="h1db021ebg74c0g46c1gaa11g1b748e24c03b" version="52">Hear how your bond thrums with pleasure. Strong. Vital. Pulsing with affection.</content>
  <content contentuid="h01b93c69g5fdcg4b6fg97d5g2c277ed49091" version="53">He gave me no choice. But it's true. I often wonder - what if I'd said the right words, made the right promises?</content>
  <content contentuid="hae736673g0ec2g4830g828fgfe65b355347e" version="52">Perhaps not my greatest failure, but a sizeable one, yes. My faith in Kagha showed... poor judgement, put mildly. &lt;i&gt;Very &lt;/i&gt;mildly.</content>
  <content contentuid="h32f22294g3a14g47f4g81e8g8cdc6289ade4" version="52">She will take Vlaakith's place as Queen of the githyanki.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd49b59d4g670ag4eabga775gf059c0fb5093" version="52">You betray yourselves. A bond based on lies will one day be severed.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb825053fg4ca0g4f0aga5b0g8544cb3fa34d" version="52">I say you'd better start looking for your true love, because it's not me.</content>
  <content contentuid="h11ba4ddfg1b7cg46fcg8064g3da60bd6e874" version="53">It is true. Nature suffered, while I dawdled, and allowed myself to be distracted.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1eb8c5adg3a9bg4056ga72bgd4b8dbbbc52a" version="51">Your love is one few have - cherish it.</content>
  <content contentuid="h59f6b2b3g177dg4073gb1fag3dfdf0aa737f" version="52">That haunts me more than anything they did to me.</content>
  <content contentuid="h19981ed1gc352g428cga641g704b0983271a" version="52">Gladly. We each know the other's heart to the fullest - there is little to fear here.</content>
  <content contentuid="h62fb4fb7gae37g4531g8116g65f08bf8303d" version="53">Her face still haunts me. If I could make the sun rise in the west, reverse the Chionthar's waters, I'd spare her my folly.</content>
  <content contentuid="he4603170ga5ebg40c6gb6e3g86af7c4dc56a" version="51">What do you say, Shadowheart? Do you want to try this?</content>
  <content contentuid="hae1501ceg0458g4d33g9560g41105bfaa92f" version="53">I'd rather have my horns yanked out with a tweezers. Come on, give me a little &lt;i&gt;action.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="h4d1f3c84geb8fg49c2g98a4g14fbead1f027" version="53">I have worse failings, I fear. Far worse.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbf902ce7gb6a7g4305ga196g9e4eb602dad4" version="52">I thought you may have bestowed the honour on someone else. But if this is what you wish, so be it.</content>
  <content contentuid="h969661e5g419fg44d0g8d09g62069b98ddd2" version="52">I don't think so. But I appreciate the offer.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc067a716gaf3eg4577gb20ag34e95d5d0449" version="51">That he somehow let some scrawny goblins capture him.</content>
  <content contentuid="hdbf58986ge329g4e6fg9136g7b225b96dab3" version="51">What do you say, Shadowheart?</content>
  <content contentuid="h2a377d95g0afbg4d82g94eegfd8f99149a39" version="52">Oh yes. Yes please. </content>
  <content contentuid="hb9942cafgcf84g4c7cga027g4ac97ecd17ad" version="52">Comfort doesn't come naturally to him - he's restless and roaming.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb9748342gc8a2g43cega61dgf4768a96dad4" version="53">You know me as I know myself. Glory be to my queen.</content>
  <content contentuid="h72d93c5fg3a41g408agb9b5g4b44b40bb242" version="53">This wretch following in your worm wake won't help you. Your bond is brittle, the kind the tyrant longs to break.</content>
  <content contentuid="he4be8eb3g5e98g402dg8984gfe4f4ab91493" version="52">This could be fun, Karlach. What do you think?</content>
  <content contentuid="h333d9613g98f6g4079g90adg8d4834413cd8" version="53">He's happy right now - look at that smile!</content>
  <content contentuid="hd1251891g1191g45eeg9149gad32907c12bd" version="52">Failing her goddess when it counted the most.</content>
  <content contentuid="h2c8ffc5bg5836g441egbd3age167e351009d" version="51">Have you come beg-begging, sniffing for our stones? Gortash won't like that. A throat his black hand can't choke the spit from. </content>
  <content contentuid="h1a2d8d8dgf6e4g45f8g82cdga3bed83a3912" version="51">There is violence afoot. Until it is resolved, I cannot in good conscience see any customers. Guard yourself, little one.</content>
  <content contentuid="haec2ccb4g0135g4d74g9198g769ec07c55af" version="52">Saving his friend Thaniel and banishing the shadow curse.</content>
  <content contentuid="h08947bcag07f8g479cg9904gee5eff49f5e4" version="53">Ha! Well, when you look this good...</content>
  <content contentuid="h74cdd0a6g070fg412ega688g19a5965d4535" version="51">&lt;i&gt;Leave.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="h8311525eg24abg40acgb6e4g16294faeb6ea" version="52">She can't swim.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8881c83dg4987g4722g84e8g81820c5cd60b" version="52">I'd sooner slice off both my hands and feed them to a rabid boar.</content>
  <content contentuid="h4a8b8989g1856g4621ga886gfd6ca0f4729a" version="52">Your bond will not save you. He will wrap its cord around your neck and make you swing from it.</content>
  <content contentuid="haa107432g4eadg4948gac34gaa4321ccb853" version="51">Return a time anew. With hearts, as well as pockets, full.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc52c780cg355fg48aegbca8gf448631ebbbb" version="52">I've had a little stone caught in my boot the last while - clearly that makes for a better travelling companion than you do.&lt;br&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="hed6352f6g9c27g4f0dg9fadge4afc40fec80" version="55">Karlach: her fire within can incinerate an enemy or warm a beloved.</content>
  <content contentuid="h144c6605gf71cg4210g8b09g4123ac689526" version="53">I see. Are you sure you don't want to quit while you're behind?</content>
  <content contentuid="haad03d7egd410g4c70g86d7gb9547c4cc07a" version="52">This is the truth. I sense I will never surpass that moment, when nature awoke from its nightmare.</content>
  <content contentuid="h522b2e90g6dd7g4b2cg9684g2cd11f6174c4" version="54">What would you know of K'liir? I trained, I studied, I excelled. I had no need of friends.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha8848172g11e4g4bc7g9cbcg6db40ee93535" version="51">Nonsense - my faith remains strong. Do you think so little of me that you'd believe this?</content>
  <content contentuid="hbad53ee6g5d78g4d77g970cg6a3cdac74731" version="51">His physique. Who can blame him?</content>
  <content contentuid="h0e8af40ag6b08g4ff4g994cg5ff6384cea39" version="54">Yes. But be warned - I play to win.</content>
  <content contentuid="h193e47ebg6c5bg41dcgbc56g13ff9bb60262" version="52">That which needs to be said is often the most difficult. Take pride - you are one step closer to conquering your fears.</content>
  <content contentuid="h75c7cf74geb78g43d2g98a2ge713a2313b35" version="52">Me.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1628867eg7c85g4076g842bg993bbdad6426" version="57">A pity. I thought your bond a mighty oak. Instead, it is kindling - a brush of fire shall make it crumble.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf90e784fg43f1g43fdg8659g9df83ea50d56" version="52">Do not worry, slaughter kin. My blades are still sharp and sweet. They will greet you soon enough.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb1e008begea21g481ag8d37g107aa8da7c25" version="52">...Boo? Does our friend know another Minsc? One that they might be courting, perhaps?</content>
  <content contentuid="h2b65a2acgd24bg4040g807ega9449d22f24f" version="52">She will live in perpetuity as a &lt;i&gt;kith'rak&lt;/i&gt; atop a red dragon.</content>
  <content contentuid="h46249846gff64g4a3cg8b10g1da1f9dcbfbd" version="54">You return, &lt;i&gt;stira&lt;/i&gt;. Shall I look into your hearts, yours and your beloved's both, and see if your love will stand the test of time? ([GEN_CheckMagicPocketGold_6057ad05-9492-4630-9f0a-be548b134c54])</content>
  <content contentuid="h427dee4ag3764g4f39g9770gcef9ef4f84d3" version="51">Listen. Think. Who does she loathe above all others?</content>
  <content contentuid="h529c03ceg5f37g4484ga800g4ebf84b0aace" version="51">Hm? Oh, the dryad is comely enough - but you? Don't poke at questions you don't want the answer to, cub.</content>
  <content contentuid="h21192471g95a5g4d0aga142g0e3a5f5078e5" version="53">What do you think, Halsin? Shall we put ourselves to the test?</content>
  <content contentuid="hf8ecaa2bgb7adg4a5eg8312g8c87e5ca1274" version="53">You let such ruptured creatures swim in your blood wake. One little skull poke and you forget how to drown them.</content>
  <content contentuid="h91cd1cb5g3cbbg4b06ga720gbe79a955cef5" version="52">She doesn't know who she is, or where she belongs.</content>
  <content contentuid="h22450661g761bg4f6fg8137gf3ef323670b2" version="53">I do not know what weakness of mine allowed them to take me. </content>
  <content contentuid="h62177b2cgfe91g444bg8d72g7bdf0ba89cb5" version="53">The heart is fraught, so let us begin with the joyous. When is he happiest?</content>
  <content contentuid="hd014dfbcg8aeag4977ga6d9ga80d79aa3735" version="52">The creature need not look into our hearts to see that I barely tolerate your existence.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha77afa9eg28b3g4a39g9c24gf678e16b076a" version="52">Oh I like that answer. Yes, let's go with that.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd6a3dc1fgecaag4b10g8affg67d82cb7accc" version="52">Sounds magical - what say you, Gale?</content>
  <content contentuid="hbcdb6614g23abg496dg9788g48f17472ec34" version="53">When he's elbow-deep in gore.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0a362800gc7fdg4522g800ege160347a154f" version="51">Sparing me and becoming a devil.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8ea4e6a4g0cadg4beegb12eg48b4aa5f936f" version="53">Sparing Karlach and becoming a devil.</content>
  <content contentuid="h218aef65g0d0cg450cgaffeg9b54b4c43e94" version="52">Hah! Absolutely. This is gonna be great fun.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb4e22c0cgdd07g459bgabfcg0786fb07fb85" version="53">Nobody.</content>
  <content contentuid="hff489756g8b6bg47a7gacceg9463e46ee73c" version="54">Well observed. There is no fouler scent - and no &lt;i&gt;sweeter&lt;/i&gt; - than that of a neogi's blood.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf85d2b85gb91bg4aa9gbfa9g6cfa2f268866" version="52">Appointing a fanatic as his second-in-command at the grove.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb9f3640fga23dg4f6agbadegf61a55307c10" version="51">Many things delight the heart, but only one makes it sing. Tell me, what is the githyanki's fondest memory?</content>
  <content contentuid="hb3341a99g1f40g46a6g99dcg8c904b9e31e7" version="51">Lae'zel: passions of the heart and the blade wage war in her soul.</content>
  <content contentuid="h21e58ddeg28fcg4d92ga8f0g846ccafb1d95" version="56">Bring the one you love to me. I will look into your hearts and see if your love is eternal. Or doomed eternally. ([GEN_CheckMagicPocketGold_6057ad05-9492-4630-9f0a-be548b134c54])</content>
  <content contentuid="h61bd3bb2g9a86g4b78g98b1g19d53256fdd8" version="52">You'd have been right, not so long ago. But things have changed - a different time, a different Blade.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc7ee8187gb6aeg483eg9ae8g0795e1fa9bbd" version="54">Oh my love, how could I say no?</content>
  <content contentuid="hf77790a1g7885g4608g8fcbgcb1eeb220941" version="53">This was good fun! You know me fairly well, it turns out.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb6685dc1gd5a2g463cgacc5gbacd542aac59" version="53">I wish I could play, but I seem to be a little short.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8b285eeeg2b36g40f7gbf06g7ca2d6d2aecf" version="52">Do you think so little of me? At least you didn't compare me to a spotted dick...</content>
  <content contentuid="hed6a7badg2cd7g4ac0gb4begb7ec0b829eed" version="52">Mmm, I don't think so. Seems a little... I don't know. Just no.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd6b1d49cg1d71g4f9dg97b6ge3a718f3d8ed" version="52">You know my heart, and I am glad. You are the first.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd9ca8e02g173ag41a3ga660geaf1031d6374" version="52">Thoroughly magical. Let's have at it.</content>
  <content contentuid="h08e55282g6a69g4a08g8838gf8bbac6a500d" version="53">No, you are mistaken. Rejecting unwanted advances is no failure, even if it earned me some scars.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8695a9fcg6178g4badg82adg68a6d26aeefd" version="53">I will be feared, this much is true. As a monster? No. As a champion? Most certainly.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9ec9f1e2gf764g49e7gb2b6gf6999c832e45" version="52">How close you are. Two hearts beating a perfect rhythm.</content>
  <content contentuid="he6428db4g7c38g4b8eg875ege310bc38fe31" version="51">Halsin: nature's gentle steward - and furious defender.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd8a95bb2gb68eg4dfega675g5ab84458635f" version="52">Many pass through our lives, their touch rippling across time. But who does Minthara admire the most?</content>
  <content contentuid="he1265173gdc5fg43e1g911dg3f8f18657756" version="52">The heart is fraught, so let us turn to the joyous. When is Gale happiest?</content>
  <content contentuid="h4aae61b5g6839g4984g8fcdgb53e501ac2c3" version="52">A three-day-old pot of tavern stew - muddled and questionable.</content>
  <content contentuid="h40ddc938g4adag4028g95f8gb6bf6958b3ec" version="52">Really? I mean, yes, but - really? You'd tell whatever stranger just walked up and asked?</content>
  <content contentuid="h8ef1a689g6a74g4e09gb6c3g251d99ed2619" version="52">Spiced Ulaver wine and thinly sliced rothé steak.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc1d71976g3abfg450fg85fcga592f93fe18d" version="53">Bring the one you love. I will look into your hearts and see if your love is eternal. Or doomed eternally.</content>
  <content contentuid="h27743261gba56g4963g8089geb976d710374" version="52">Probably dead.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha4d00e78g4316g4db8g877fg47a151774426" version="53">Minthara, my dear, shall we show this dryad how it's done?</content>
  <content contentuid="hb7c19b9dgcb9bg4843gb0a6g1b0f93fb29e9" version="54">Yes - a hero in all senses. A courageous explorer and a just spirit. A pity to see what's become of him.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha685c73agc36eg4f86g8176ga61e18875b51" version="51">But I must move on. Nature demands that I do.</content>
  <content contentuid="h55f6c030gf2d9g4cfcg91ffg3d33344e4d33" version="52">The sweetest loves dance lightly on the tongue. But they sag and suffer with age. The future brings many trials.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9c8fcab0g9984g41b0gb462ge70716899baf" version="53">She's nice. But I'm more of a sunlight girl myself.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd9684cdcgbe52g41d7g97beg996364d8fa88" version="53">I barely remember the grove... I was not myself. But my only regret is that I exerted myself in the name of a false god.</content>
  <content contentuid="h694d5693gdabbg494cg8ce1g3e868002d195" version="53">Fall for me.</content>
  <content contentuid="h54b9eebag56b4g4ab4g965bg926bd49e21c3" version="52">To annoy Shadowheart.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5186578cgea88g4e8bgb419g7e4e9c4ac4d4" version="52">No. Just no.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7f254712g0646g4f69ga486g6ab9a64e88fd" version="52">Ah, the fruit of scholars. How I long to have a troop of loyal students grace me with apples by the orchard-full in exchange for wisdoms imparted...</content>
  <content contentuid="hc4817100g15a6g4377gb3d8g70dfed5c899b" version="52">Pleasant, &lt;i&gt;vivid &lt;/i&gt;memories, yes. But my greatest source of pride? No.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc2b53d89g0e09g4f33g8f5fg0e83c6397fd0" version="52">Being kind to animals.</content>
  <content contentuid="h42bf8606g169ag4fabgb63dg75427a260431" version="53">Making a pact with Mizora.</content>
  <content contentuid="haffb1fc8g0895g4d39ga362ga012c5283129" version="53">Everyone loves - even those who wrap their hearts in stone. I can help you see that love more clearly.</content>
  <content contentuid="h4bea9da9g44e3g43cag9907gd6f4711e7ca9" version="51">Excuse me? I've been happy, thank you very much.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd1582e55g49a8g4393gb05fg30fa66881055" version="53">In Mystra's embrace.</content>
  <content contentuid="h40bff375gaab3g4e9egb329gf6dbd79a355a" version="53">Well put. Though I'll forgive a middling wine so long as the company makes up the difference...</content>
  <content contentuid="hb5b05730g4a2bg4742g902bg5aea65103a22" version="52">Fine. But if this creature can truly look into my heart, it best be careful what it reveals.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6fe48972g37c2g4f60g8520g99d79ae44835" version="53">Well, Minsc - what say we give it a go?&lt;br&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="h5decb16cg0b2fg4d76g8f8agb1188c0eb269" version="52">A vicious monster of legend, feared across the planes.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbef637a5ga3d6g450dg8081gb571a66c5063" version="55">Your bond beats in pleasure. It is an honour to behold.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc9e23391g1767g4093g828cg5f2d2db0181e" version="53">Picking off her siblings one by one.</content>
  <content contentuid="h378a2b4cgeaf7g4634ga349g1fab30dbceb9" version="53">Mm. I took my pleasure, and it was done. I've devoted few thoughts to it since.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc1bf5c9fg587ag4716g8f6eg7e774c3fca4d" version="51">Listen. Think. What, on his darkest day, would make him smile?</content>
  <content contentuid="hfc191fc7g57ffg42f8g97dfg8cb9f2fadde1" version="52">Truly spoken. All he'd done for Baldur's Gate, for its people... He earned a better fate than the one Gortash gave him.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7d05c2aegafc0g450bga974geb088dc1395e" version="54">You are wise to admit it. When it comes to love, vulnerability is armour. Truth, a sword. And trust, a shield. I pray you wield all three, &lt;i&gt;stira&lt;/i&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h48e4f284g41eeg4656ga405gdfc207bf995a" version="51">I have no time for love.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7411a504gf0a7g4539gafb8g1f83f85a071c" version="52">There was no love to be found. My mother would have poisoned her own milk to torment me.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf11e4773gb3a8g49dcga62dga191086a5ddb" version="53">I suppose I should be grateful - you helped me shed any illusions that you might have been paying attention. &lt;i&gt;Thank you&lt;/i&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb9cd06edgb1f1g44a3gba0bge89880b26358" version="52">Violence erupts here - my home. My refuge in this city of stone and steel. Solace escapes me...</content>
  <content contentuid="hb90fede8g121eg41b0gbb0bg9c4474dfe8a0" version="51">A blanket?</content>
  <content contentuid="h7fbcb099g78acg4ac9gae81g76392c560ebd" version="53">Your bond is false, and I know why. Because your heart belongs to another.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc1a69c51g9758g4932gb447gebc7d33536a2" version="51">We cannot live this life without others - others to guide us. To aspire to. Who does the Blade most admire?</content>
  <content contentuid="h8cf17ad8ga1f6g476bg8d71g9ee2daebe800" version="53">&lt;i&gt;Chk.&lt;/i&gt; I don't see the harm.</content>
  <content contentuid="hfd8dc60bga94fg4671gb356g3786a636b266" version="53">You confuse fiction for fact. Even at my most loyal, I never longed for the githyanki throne.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd66f5df7g268bg4e61gb1f2g8939b8209c4a" version="52">I would not be ascended - not by my own will, and not by Vlaakith's. Are you truly so indifferent to me?</content>
  <content contentuid="h4b0f238dg73b9g4d33ga405g03105820fd4c" version="52">Spiders are Lolth's creatures - as was I. Her cult controlled me just as the Absolute did. Not a pleasant memory at all.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha2632b01g6fbag4eafg89c2g5e0b8d3992cd" version="52">Why not? Could be good for a laugh.</content>
  <content contentuid="h16b0ce9ag8db6g4dddgaf4cgf452c347c402" version="52">This sounds like fun, Wyll. Want to try?</content>
  <content contentuid="h1d5942a7g0f05g414ag878dg771fb5ab8927" version="53">Life is brief - finite. When the warrior dies, what legacy will she leave behind?</content>
  <content contentuid="h6ef5179fg3a45g4b02g85f4ge892d11c4b51" version="52">Sacrificing an innocent for her own ambitions.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3ada6c19g2c78g42d4gb6cag57c0f5180a9c" version="51">At his study in the grove.</content>
  <content contentuid="h167eb82fgc391g433dg9017g99fff84eb562" version="52">Mindless gorging...? No, that is not right. I did not realise you thought that of me.</content>
  <content contentuid="he11b07afgdddcg49e9g9df7g7b67afc7fabf" version="54">Your love may be wanting, little one, but your heart will find its path.</content>
  <content contentuid="he06f4498ge382g446bgbd90g0537b1c65bac" version="52">An impressively notched bedpost.</content>
  <content contentuid="h23042ca1g56f6g403cgacbcg17fcb0f40cf6" version="52">I suppose we've braved greater dangers together than public embarrassment. Do as you wish.</content>
  <content contentuid="h677f5205gf8eeg4a53ga0fdg78e4b6490355" version="52">I see how you slip-slither closer, belly dragging in the filth. Father is &lt;i&gt;laughing&lt;/i&gt; at you.</content>
  <content contentuid="h60d6a456gbc35g496dgb9c9g787c07c28b89" version="52">Mizora.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb008cb20g8bd7g44b4g987dg59dfee7a1b63" version="52">Are we finished? You were only mildly disappointing. Well done.</content>
  <content contentuid="h77815c5fg6c36g4452gbe65g1b90fa3bc9c5" version="52">Not just siblings. Androcide, senicide, avunculicide - I only regret I left before enjoying a matricide. That would be a memory to cherish.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8a4592cagad82g463eg9b0bg12e31f75b2ef" version="52">A roast onion - versatile, with hidden layers.</content>
  <content contentuid="h37f6c592g8548g4994g94b1g76db708b1b94" version="52">I know my heart - and yours - better than this creature ever will. But we can indulge it if you wish.</content>
  <content contentuid="hca09a8ddge2b4g415cgbbb2g8b4992d3b7d5" version="52">He thinks he, and the world, might be better off if he were dead.</content>
  <content contentuid="h23a580f6gd674g45bcg845ag8e6e55f9d60a" version="53">Guilty as charged. Sometimes literally...</content>
  <content contentuid="h6e91ed65g0fccg4931g8539g4b5b50b81d05" version="52">Presumptious. But not inaccurate. You have earned my companionship - that is no easy task.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha175bfa4g40e8g4634g8bacge463ca9d62ab" version="53">Well. I think we've proven here today that we really don't know each other very well, do we? Ah well. There's time.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9069c577g2d47g45cbg851bg64e59c98ab49" version="52">Spurning an amorous she-bear's affections.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9d25e08fg3565g48b5gb380gd90f38d63f17" version="53">A nice, tasty rat.</content>
  <content contentuid="h57809bc6g3bfeg4f4cga474g3e6cc458b83a" version="53">Settled down in a quiet village with a nice partner and a few kids.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1469dc46g5eaag414cgb6c9gc223968ef76e" version="52">Excuse you! I think not. Not ever.</content>
  <content contentuid="h46752909g0a1eg4ebcg87a5gb161ad32df83" version="51">Allowing the shadow curse to blight nature for a hundred years.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8c4b13b1gc459g462cg9770g20284a2a2f2d" version="52">You understand me almost perfectly. Only my late mother may have bested you.</content>
  <content contentuid="heed8cca1g3ff3g4622gb6eege544bcfc1de0" version="51">I suggest you stop speaking - for your own health, of course.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha9af8de1g9649g4780gb700g5bbb69a44445" version="57">Listen. Think. From where does Shadowheart draw comfort on a cold, dark night?</content>
  <content contentuid="h2e704c8age60cg4a9fg8638g2273d2075483" version="53">You really know me, don't you? It's wild. In so many ways, we barely know each other. But where it counts, you're deeper in my head than that tadpole.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb39c63adg9c3dg4fa9g880fg5a0cdf7918dd" version="51">Gortash knows you are coming. Knows you have the Bone Lord's stone. Do not let him hiss hot air into your worm-weakened brain.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbe859e9ag89c3g4703g9b6ag9f7a007e66a8" version="54">Killing Karlach.</content>
  <content contentuid="h862781e6gd7e2g405dga536gb481aab0ba65" version="52">Being discreet.</content>
  <content contentuid="h2d7a73a9gc568g4554g9e2fgb0f49ae5d01b" version="53">Oh I'm the one you love? Well my dear, how could I say no?</content>
  <content contentuid="h88ef7c18g349eg4290gb785gfc45b1b9fdd5" version="51">It will simply not be with one another. Farewell.</content>
  <content contentuid="h61933c74ga583g41e5gad22g2104052ff17a" version="51">Close your eyes, and she will show herself to you.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5b38144agdf8bg4feagbdceg28c37df72a40" version="52">Minsc is flattered, but surely you must know that his heart is already of the hamster shape. And twice as fuzzy.</content>
  <content contentuid="h48bc048dgf076g4b20gb090g258b34308ea2" version="53">His father, Ulder Ravengard.</content>
  <content contentuid="h15ca133bg0245g43b2ga2f2g683abc1ec35f" version="51">Remember - his throat spits lies, but my blade carves the truth. You will read it on your skin soon enough.</content>
  <content contentuid="h874ad50ag12b6g4828g9ed8g4c3e0e872c75" version="51">You hear my words, you see my path. It is good to be &lt;i&gt;known&lt;/i&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="hed898517g4c4eg4914gb83fg57f096529ccd" version="53">Freedom.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7f1b5ce1g5d75g44d0g9647gf3e8a70e67c9" version="53">Breaking a nail.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5f32e3c5g753cg46d4g83a0g3946a8f00cea" version="52">Well, if you insist...</content>
  <content contentuid="h9568d026g5aaag4746gb1eeg6dd06d527563" version="53">I'd be highly entertained if he choked on a button. But I don't &lt;i&gt;hate &lt;/i&gt;him, per se.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6d64700fg0c97g4754ga19cg5722d2b82def" version="54">I'm more than game. Let's do it.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5b3c2ee7g6654g40abga7fcgdab8bf2a3f00" version="51">Listen. Think. What does she most desire?</content>
  <content contentuid="h63a5a91fgf70fg42aag86f8gd936f4136df7" version="52">I suppose I should be grateful - you helped me shed any illusions that you've been paying attention.</content>
  <content contentuid="h20ddeb2egf21bg4521g849dge1a7178a2895" version="52">Spilling her own cousins' blood.</content>
  <content contentuid="h72d90023gf53cg4f50g84f8ged063651ff56" version="52">A sweet gesture, but all... this? It's not really for me.</content>
  <content contentuid="h18bf9627g1d45g4b26g8dd1gefa4bfadaa42" version="52">Astarion, are you up for this?</content>
  <content contentuid="he066ea20g7a87g4b2bg9014g9e3b964550f3" version="52">No, that is not right. My body is but a vessel to serve nature with. To take pride in it is to indulge in vanity.</content>
  <content contentuid="hedb0d73ag9255g42f9gbb1ag1973259880b4" version="52">I had always kept my heart hidden, but I allowed you to see it. To see me. It saddens me that you saw a stranger instead.&lt;br&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="hbfb4f096g8da7g4e74gac97gaa4e38e57a8e" version="51">A decade from now, what will the mighty Karlach do? Where will she be?</content>
  <content contentuid="hebf54e7cgb246g4e71gbf5cg0272c8fe692a" version="52">This is the truth - I live for the wilderness. Comfort is for the farm animal, snug in its pen.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5cf33d46gb811g4555ga8d0g092e1b527eb3" version="53">Sharp wooden sticks.</content>
  <content contentuid="h151161ecg6285g45c8gb264g0b4ae43ab3d4" version="52">Gortash.</content>
  <content contentuid="h32c9af1cg6754g434agbffagaf517f6071b5" version="52">Jaheira, this could be entertaining - let's give it a go.&lt;br&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="h383811c9g7d79g41a8ga7f2gbe4b60e361f9" version="52">It can't hurt, I suppose - unless you embarrass me. Then you might find yourself hurting in a whole manner of ways.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha102569bg7e8eg4d63g9f05g386ecbe3e058" version="52">There is a great love amongst you - Zethino senses it. Bring your leader to me, and we shall see if your love is that of ages.</content>
  <content contentuid="h73a117b4g5411g4f97g99c4g32944e4a13c6" version="51">I cannot, little one. I can accept truth, and only truth - and you know that is not what lies within your hearts.</content>
  <content contentuid="he35e295egf54dg4e8dg92d2g3117240530d9" version="53">To find the truth about Orpheus amidst her queen's lies.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd2a5ba9fg3e95g45c5gb25bgf16cbef6a75a" version="51">You remind me of her.</content>
  <content contentuid="h65ed3a69gddb9g4ae4g98ddg6038a64236b3" version="52">To ascend.</content>
  <content contentuid="hef0e82f7g5443g40aegbce4gccaf52aea877" version="52">Hardly. Astonishing that you'd even utter her name.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf947c602g3ad0g4628g80e9gceedcd07a3b8" version="51">It is true. Surface food lacks flavour. House Baenre banquets were legendary.</content>
  <content contentuid="h290c926dgb17dg41cdg8b0cgb42963605a8a" version="53">Spending time with her beloved family.</content>
  <content contentuid="hdeb16209ga086g45e9gaf95gab82278f3286" version="53">Bashing baddies interspersed with victory sex.</content>
  <content contentuid="h657fe077gf9a2g47c5g8202g16e9c41c2342" version="51">I will carry the truth to my people, whatever it might mean. Only time will tell how I'm remembered.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb09a2636g54b8g4baag8a5bg4d7b7bb3534a" version="54">I have someone in mind - let me go get them.</content>
  <content contentuid="h981f1c7bgb2fbg4407gb986ga5ac53340269" version="53">I don't think he's ever been happy.</content>
  <content contentuid="h2c1bfc85g0877g4600gb4cbg0a7b67a90303" version="53">Not completely off the mark, but there's easier paths into my good graces...</content>
  <content contentuid="h73da91c5g035cg49c8gae06g1c23972c03ca" version="52">Kids, huh? I don't know. How about a really mean goat.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5705e535g133ag4121gb211g16cca4032519" version="51">Most things fear him, actually.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1675e2ffgae42g449agb7d2g81e401a06732" version="51">I could end it now - but I'll be patient. Father will see us together again. He will see you bleed.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb119c055g60c2g49c5g97f8gad5c38b1e959" version="54">But I know the truth. Only one face haunts your dreams each night. Close your eyes, sweetness, and she will come to you...</content>
  <content contentuid="h327f8bcegc5ddg4da9gbdbdg02b1cd0e5994" version="55">Your bond tears but it does not break - have hope.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc5559297g3e80g4991ga4d8g4849a3220e6a" version="51">I do love someone - someone close to me, actually.</content>
  <content contentuid="hcde5d757g7c07g44a7g8cbcgd64ce5a503fd" version="51">Astarion: a tumultuous past hides behind a mirthful grin.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9ba59937gec86g4df9gacabgce11d57618bf" version="51">We strive to do our utmost - to prove ourselves worthy. Tell me - of what is Halsin most proud?</content>
  <content contentuid="h8788122dg3c31g473fgba7dgc723f9aa115b" version="51">A mug of nutty darndarr and a plate of cured meats? It's no Mount Celestia - but it's close.</content>
  <content contentuid="hca8b106cg25d9g484fga604gd4e649ddd8d7" version="56">Close your eyes, little ones. Be still as stone to earth. And remember to breathe.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0ddaaf1dge181g42feg910fgcf4a3e22e58a" version="53">Balduran, the great hero of Baldur's Gate.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha2575939gf3a3g4aa4g95bcge445090962a0" version="52">How about it, Lae'zel? Want to give it a go?</content>
  <content contentuid="ha1df6605gd1c2g4111g9204g69d141d0a2ba" version="52">The closeness of her kin at Crèche K'liir.</content>
  <content contentuid="h877e228eg9d47g4961gbf0cgb06f5becd730" version="52">Hells. Have I fallen so far from your favour?</content>
  <content contentuid="h2271a9e1g35bdg4f33gbb30g15f85993aeba" version="53">Me.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6d9f7d29g413bg4b15ga09ag0409f2d80fb3" version="54">All we have seen, all that has changed, and you still cling to old crusades.</content>
  <content contentuid="h88ccaa75gd6ddg4c38g9263g7ea1eaf39850" version="52">But no, there's absolutely no way this is happening.</content>
  <content contentuid="had2ea0cag5ec7g4b89ga9edg6ef78553140e" version="53">Forever feeling like a slave to someone else.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0b9dbdc9g835fg4f22g81e6g453b3a42ec59" version="52">May he be at peace. We did not see eye to eye, but his every thought, every act, was in service to his people. Among men, there was none greater.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7d59b17age8bcg4dc5g950bg57f19e474f16" version="52">You waste time soft-soothing these flesh bags for the knife.</content>
  <content contentuid="h36ece013gb05eg416bgbac6g88d2b525d9be" version="53">Bah - trivialities. Have you been so inattentive?</content>
  <content contentuid="h15995c74g3aedg470fgb8ccge59702f28c84" version="57">Shadowheart: an endless storm surges behind sharp eyes.</content>
  <content contentuid="he4b5100bgc1dfg4abegaf58g7138087a5504" version="52">But perhaps fate can yet be defied...</content>
  <content contentuid="hcec02cbcg65f6g4ee1g89d5ge0d5c6c5e417" version="55">Me.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9e2b8b8dg9b8cg4668gae69ga30797c20053" version="52">With you? Please. That story's written in stone, and it ends with you on one side of the world and me on the other.</content>
  <content contentuid="h936f1926g879fg4c9agbc86g24c7260489aa" version="51">Bah - my people already know liberty. Once, the illithids enslaved us; thanks to Vlaakith, we remain free.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1c1912c6g8aa2g4ba8g92e0gb45149e8274f" version="53">You're very funny, did I ever mention that?</content>
  <content contentuid="h87a9d339g114ag4996g82ccgc0c1c082d3a0" version="53">The night itself.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd7087602g272dg4b09gb8ebgc9bbbe59721a" version="51">So you're the lickspittle who crushed the Bone Lord's thrall.</content>
  <content contentuid="h35599283g5a78g4fb0gb5cdg5110e4a89537" version="52">Once, perhaps. But those passions have soured.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7839c6f3g79e9g4938g9826ga243a915889f" version="53">Hardly. My association with you might be a contender after that attempt...</content>
  <content contentuid="h025ed64fgf2c8g434fg9f05g54b6c876780f" version="54">What do I say? Melon... donkey... sunrise? Whichever words will get you to leave me out of this.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8557b35cg398ag491bg881fg902694089c9a" version="51">Protecting his grove from those who threatened it.</content>
  <content contentuid="h20b92ea6g6730g4e4dga97dg08a663f7fd51" version="53">I press my finger to your bond and find a shield - impenetrable. It is... beautiful.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3b87b71cgfff3g4d0dg8b83g415637deb604" version="52">Love blossoms in life's furies - you have formed bonds in this time, have you not? Trust. Respect. These are clothes that love dresses in.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc2151cb7g430dg491cga0feg6ced3304cbf1" version="51">When you find the lordling, tell him Orin is watching.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc808b797gd38eg4569gbcb3g6ba3b90d72df" version="51">Do not fear - there is time yet. For our touch has been light, but now we must dig deep - deeper than any other.</content>
  <content contentuid="h51530bf6g402eg41b8ga3a4g310d7639ecfc" version="52">She will be known as a liberator of the githyanki people.</content>
  <content contentuid="h61621822ga509g477ag8976g10520f6b514d" version="52">Perhaps you're overestimating my affection towards you a tad? You'd better seek a partner-in-embarrassment elsewhere.</content>
  <content contentuid="h04f7b315g337eg423fg8445g5f886c2e94dc" version="53">You're not wrong, but do we need to tell every stranger we meet our business?</content>
  <content contentuid="h236c0cd3gfc4eg43e1gb7f8g49f03eadc571" version="51">The knowledge that she can change, just as sure as night will give way to day.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf951692fg0bd2g4ed6gb6cfg7cbe607beb48" version="52">A flagon of ale.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5f0f21ddg4ab2g4d28gae38g884f613948cb" version="51">Wyll: the courageous heart tormented by the infernal.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9909fc88g497ag4677gbafeg5b15d0bb8f01" version="51">The heart craves comfort, but needs &lt;i&gt;respect&lt;/i&gt;. How does one earn the dark-haired maiden's respect?</content>
  <content contentuid="h5e9fd788gdfaag47ffg8c8agea48350c98ba" version="52">A small delight, indeed. I did not want their friendship - I wanted their &lt;i&gt;fear&lt;/i&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h82947778gd5f0g4f10g976cg6b373de0513f" version="52">Leaving behind his father - and his city.</content>
  <content contentuid="h75159da7g6536g4056gb38dg65a27f3b4016" version="53">While on his balcony in Waterdeep.</content>
  <content contentuid="h76e23dc9gfc6bg4e24gb51bge574ba621ad5" version="52">A necessary step for my city's future. The Hells' fires ran red hot that day; I don't remember it fondly.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6a45d32agf996g44c9g9be9gf28040e9467a" version="52">You have already sought Zethino's guidance, little one. Nurture and protect your love - for it is one of life's most precious gifts.</content>
  <content contentuid="h326f0b75g593bg4bf8gb893gd8f57ae84672" version="53">Let herself be captured by the cult of the Absolute.</content>
  <content contentuid="h731ca5e4ga05fg4f75gae1bgb136691b0b9b" version="53">You know me, you understand me. And for that, I'm forever grateful.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1d78fb46g8015g4c0eg8278gc100175e043c" version="52">I should know not to underestimate you. You see me with clear eyes and open mind. </content>
  <content contentuid="h0e33c1d0g006fg4145gaea2g557d2162cbdc" version="52">But... I don't know. Things can change I guess. I've heard.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha3a3cb57g2848g4cf1gae00gadcfeb6fdb46" version="53">Strolling through town window shopping.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5c4cfc0ag93e9g45d5gaaccged7da8fb9fd7" version="52">Your words are cruel, but your heart quivers. Love is a tangled forest - there is no shame in seeking guidance. Think on it.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc03e721egc7e9g4decg804ag8b522f38f438" version="55">Your eyes, &lt;i&gt;stira&lt;/i&gt;. There is pain, endless and deep. But also devotion - blazing like the sun. You're in love, are you not?</content>
  <content contentuid="ha287abc7g5321g4225g9e77g5a173ecf8dbb" version="51">Go in peace, seedlings. And know that you made one whose heart was long quiet beat with love anew.</content>
  <content contentuid="h421029bcg8bfcg4651g9e83gc8f1ab6ad247" version="54">Well, that was a disaster. Can we call time on this farce? Please?</content>
  <content contentuid="h9a4e8264ga8b7g4923g92d7g4e1e7991a506" version="51">Self-deprecation is not endearing. It is demeaning.</content>
  <content contentuid="h86e50f42gbf84g4035g9854gb2194682dccc" version="53">Listen. Think. If the wizard were given the choice, what food would he be?</content>
  <content contentuid="hff5dc039g016dg428bgb144g4d1f183a4d45" version="52">It's a grimace, sweetie. Not off to a great start.</content>
  <content contentuid="h05341f0eg4048g4871gb1e6g832a07b835a5" version="51">The night itself.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd18e30bcgb7bag4c78ga1a2g3bba8ed41f1c" version="53">It pains me to hear you say it. We shared a bond, or so I thought. Does it mean nothing to you?</content>
  <content contentuid="h77a67cc0geb9ag460aga682g7df39767299a" version="51">Forgive me - I had not realised. My beloved, before she died, was a woman of great strength and fortitude. I called her &lt;i&gt;stira&lt;/i&gt; in our quiet moments.</content>
  <content contentuid="h447dbde3g8b7bg40f9g957egea0bd03141f7" version="52">The gods.</content>
  <content contentuid="haf6f503agd284g485cg9252gc02442ae2637" version="54">I didn't think a little game would sting so much when I agreed to this... but you're right.</content>
  <content contentuid="h60ef3a04g7ed2g4718ga9a6g3c352fbba692" version="52">Bravo. That is indeed where my mind wanders to, when times are hard...</content>
  <content contentuid="h06c097b0gdce7g415bg93beg9bc3af82f2e7" version="53">Our touch has been that of sunlight, but now we must ask the deep. The difficult.</content>
  <content contentuid="h44022908gdf33g446egbb7bg81bd9a06b68c" version="52">Yes - a hero in all senses. A courageous explorer and a just spirit. Would that we all aspired to his greatness.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf418a2ecgc39dg4616gb5fdg2819289f7af8" version="51">But do not despair, seedlings. You are young - you will find love.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8ec36ee5gcb92g4e34g96cfg9bb3899f256b" version="52">Wait, I'm the one you love? Oh no - oh that's so sad.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd546c8c7gd7dcg4ca7gabb6gad9d1102b3d0" version="52">Maybe I'd have been with him on the journey from Elturel. Maybe there'd be no Absolute, no infections, no... &lt;i&gt;this&lt;/i&gt;.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5c96cd33g09c0g412eg8309gadbec13d8d6c" version="52">It seems you've been paying attention to me - though there is always room for improvement.</content>
  <content contentuid="h07383faag3512g4cb7g9fe6ge1618b92a755" version="52">Yes, yes, yes! Let's do it!</content>
  <content contentuid="h18a1cb79gb331g4f4cga5bdg9e0131c1f69a" version="53">Our night together.</content>
  <content contentuid="h4f68fa0bgf34eg4087g8043g20b3635534ea" version="51">The bond wavers, but we have only just begun. Have faith.</content>
  <content contentuid="h45c9c587g204fg47b2gb707g649b8fcb4307" version="51">Life is a difficult and tumultuous thing. With every smile, a tear often follows. What is Wyll's greatest regret?</content>
  <content contentuid="h2444fc5cg85c4g4533g8b5ag05baa208d389" version="52">Worshipping Selûne.</content>
  <content contentuid="h63dfbd77ge5eeg4b27g8753g30eda638178e" version="53">Legendary drow hero Drizzt Do'Urden.</content>
  <content contentuid="h22921d59g1fbfg427cg9767g2a9fb00967ef" version="52">Her hair.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha04b6c31ga67bg4941ga3dfg8c8e00898dea" version="52">&lt;i&gt;Please. &lt;/i&gt;I'd rather spend my nights with a drider than with that do-gooder and his pussycat.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8c7f92cbg32b0g41d0g8609g017f25bb509a" version="52">Showing shrewd judgement.</content>
  <content contentuid="he4bf8bb8gfccfg4669gb735gd296635de890" version="53">An illuminating exercise. You've listened, if not always with both ears in attendance.</content>
  <content contentuid="h99d715ddg52a8g42c1gb789g2a77e70c8967" version="53">Memories of our first night getting to know each other.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5f922855ga196g46e2g8195g857149a3a254" version="52">You make me sound like some preening peacock. I am not &lt;i&gt;that &lt;/i&gt;bad.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3695621fg5daag4ed3g9a6fgd47afa729233" version="51">I think not. The gods are more fickle than the fools who follow them.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha3f688d9gfb89g48a6gbb36gfdd482d58458" version="52">I'm flattered, but pick another. Watching the dryad make you cry will be entertainment enough.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb9f5e727g830eg4c0dga626gbe358778728b" version="52">The Hells threatened to swallow the city. I made the only choice I could.</content>
  <content contentuid="he719ecbdg69f5g4bdbg835fgf0f8b98f7386" version="51">Zariel.</content>
  <content contentuid="h91add2c0g4d46g4c03gb2bfgaeba8374df32" version="53">Your guise may fool the others, but Zethino knows your heart - you have already sought guidance. Let others have their turn.</content>
  <content contentuid="had538ef7g08c8g42a1g929eg1511edf999fa" version="52">Your bond a seedling - one that needs a gentle hand in its tending. Nurture it and it will become a great oak, in time.</content>
  <content contentuid="hcc96a857g46f9g44f5g9716g8f3fdf7cf923" version="53">Shame sits in the soul of all - to tame it, we must &lt;i&gt;name&lt;/i&gt; it. Shadowheart - what is her deepest shame?</content>
  <content contentuid="h4d356aaeg070bg43baga423g66a290f7f2a4" version="51">Scholarly pursuits are important... but my heart lies elsewhere.</content>
  <content contentuid="h114bb78bgb204g452dgb43cga5a5a9c9f5d9" version="53">Slaughtering the tieflings at the grove.</content>
  <content contentuid="h97127e83gec2fg4859gbf5cgc33cebabd883" version="53">I have to say, you know me better than I thought. I'll have to be more mysterious in future.</content>
  <content contentuid="h80ea82edg2965g4751g944bg52995ad62fbb" version="53">I'm not right now, but whose fault is that?</content>
  <content contentuid="hb94e0ab0gb1fcg46f1ga777g74f2063c7acc" version="52">He's too enraptured by illusions and fantasies, neglecting what's real.</content>
  <content contentuid="h94ab6abagf683g45e2gbb51g45815cf2949f" version="52">Love, is it? I hadn't realised I'd bowled you over that much. Give it a try, then - impress me.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd9daec17gc4ebg4c25g9e5cg4fb8f2462008" version="53">Her pet spiders.</content>
  <content contentuid="h5fad0b63gf0eeg434dgb70dg8b8749cff263" version="53">Indeed. We've not always seen eye to eye, but his every thought, every act, was in service to his people. Among men, there is none greater.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha432d38dgce81g4564gb0fegd9d1098f212a" version="51">Do you wish to speak of love, little one? For Zethino is here to help - always. ([GEN_CheckMagicPocketGold_6057ad05-9492-4630-9f0a-be548b134c54])</content>
  <content contentuid="h675f5589g20ceg4e80g8272g6aced2932f65" version="53">A lemon meringue - tart and lightweight.</content>
  <content contentuid="h97f0b787g70d6g4c2bg846ag5cdd7669a452" version="52">Minthara: a mask of ice hides a heart of pure fire - you do well to call her close.</content>
  <content contentuid="h08cdc5d4g9a0fg467fg866ag414223d8d644" version="53">Revenge.</content>
  <content contentuid="h89c906bfg0547g4fc9g93f6g7ebea64938a3" version="52">I had high expectations, but even still, I am impressed. You may know me better than I know myself.</content>
  <content contentuid="he7fab08cg3f74g4b1ega8e3g735a5362b9cc" version="53">She's the worst of the worst. I suppose a devil can't help her nature, but she's got a really godsdamn bad nature.</content>
  <content contentuid="h657def2fg2bc2g4bb6g907bg425849eaafc1" version="52">All affections face their trials. Your bond quivers, but it does not yet break.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb1c54363g37c6g42a9gab36ge44ae80ed19b" version="54">There is a hollowness between you, something brittle and strained. We must dig deeper. Grasp the pain hiding within.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8b8e5be6g58ceg4b86gb1bfg5a3fb4e5fbd0" version="51">Why do you keep calling me '&lt;i&gt;stira&lt;/i&gt;'?</content>
  <content contentuid="h7bd6407egb748g4dd3g8433g2833c514cce0" version="59">Ah. &lt;i&gt;Glorious&lt;/i&gt;. Your bond is sweeter than nature's dew. I see you. &lt;i&gt;Know&lt;/i&gt; you. But do you know one another?</content>
  <content contentuid="h20342ce0g6864g4382g9c3eg3fb0b86e82c9" version="52">Life is full of victory and loss. You cannot have one without the other. Halsin - what is his greatest failure?</content>
  <content contentuid="hccf0add3g6b77g46bag93d3g278b41f8910a" version="51">Still rolling in the muck, I see.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9386f264g5032g4535g884cg71a6b147cb01" version="53">Sitting quietly reading a book.</content>
  <content contentuid="h2c3095afga92eg4a2eg84b3g93c54428f7c3" version="52">An... unfortunate result. Perhaps we should not have partaken.</content>
  <content contentuid="h63a810a2g6886g474bg9132gb3075c8b423a" version="52">A shiny red apple - wholesome as can be.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1304b905g16dag47a9g82a3g2ab758b8172c" version="52">Attention.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb6fe43e3gb381g49b8g99b0g77a445c3e07a" version="51">Look at it, come crawling home, hands stained with the Bone Lord's soot. And you carry his stone.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc4cfd9f4g4014g43cdgade2ge80f599bf812" version="53">Without Lolth or the Absolute, I am free for the first time. Some may call it exile, I call it independence.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd2e6c016g449dg486fgb7f9g4550aa0dfc92" version="52">He's too eager to please, no matter the cost.</content>
  <content contentuid="h47677332g45b1g4322g8fcag7ed962ffeb44" version="53">You didn't do abysmally, I suppose. That's worth something.</content>
  <content contentuid="h545990d0g208dg4e03gb371g93b3f815b238" version="52">Not today. Or any other time, come to think of it.</content>
  <content contentuid="hebfd742bg0b31g480ag8ce9ga37a0aaf6180" version="51">While in the form of a bear, clad in nothing but fur.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd5efd770g7dc3g45e6ga1f2g7ace28238d52" version="53">Very good. (Just don't say it so loud.)</content>
  <content contentuid="h86de398eg8ba6g4caeg80c9g7618f2a92823" version="53">This city of stone and steel is an endless scream in nature's womb. I have felt no peace here. Until now.</content>
  <content contentuid="h55428866gd1a1g4f00gb54ag5784fd6a62b8" version="52">Farting on a Selûnite.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8d519753g3dceg4dc0ga94cg94287c4f0dd3" version="53">Urgh, really? Of all the things you could think of - that?</content>
  <content contentuid="h0ed2fd7dg88f9g4089gb511ge8ef45c69868" version="52">An apt metaphor - though I hope it won't lose me some kisses.</content>
  <content contentuid="h16f384c1gccf0g4db2gb6fcg53326fdd5d04" version="52">Tearing the limbs from the beasts of the Sea of Night.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd1039bf5ga378g41c8gb187gb796acc3b061" version="53">Together we've shed blood, shared words. Yet you've learned so little.</content>
  <content contentuid="hdbea1fd7g0cecg4c6agbc5dg5e6e9a9acac3" version="55">The sweetest loves dance lightly on the tongue. But now we must dig deeper. Into the most painful reaches of the spirit.</content>
  <content contentuid="hed64a5e9g8b9dg4346gbc76g2ad68c603f2f" version="52">Judging others.</content>
  <content contentuid="h16dceb5ag20dfg4818gb588g39fdd98e91c3" version="52">The curse is no more, true. But imagine if I had been faster, bolder, &lt;i&gt;better&lt;/i&gt;. Lives would have been saved. More than I care to count.</content>
  <content contentuid="hae3a52b7g439bg41c4gb19cg92b6ddd2d316" version="53">Himself.</content>
  <content contentuid="hee0dc79age921g4d63g85e7g1d9d64ee2e5b" version="53">No... that wasn't my most glorious moment, but my greatest failure? Far from it.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd0ad76f5g3256g4a37ga2ffgcfd18b4e3b4d" version="52">Nature is my true love. You, I merely tolerate.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9866f877ge274g4eafg8827g9385959216f2" version="52">We often gaze through a veil of roses, but love accepts both the petal and the thorn. Gale - what is his greatest flaw?</content>
  <content contentuid="hf89931b5ga956g4cb7g8ae6g30aee352d2d2" version="53">There is no need for secrecy here. You wear your truth so close to the skin.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd498a1a9gdeb8g4216gb219gd9549d24ae1a" version="51">Never. That you live, that you walk this path, is a delight worth celebrating, not lamenting.</content>
  <content contentuid="hefcf2cc1gb43fg433dgb50cga7314d0f951e" version="52">No - we acted justly. That Karlach still lives is a delight worth celebrating, not lamenting.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9820644bg55a7g4c90g9b07gfe42dd2ca8bd" version="53">Well... You were right every time. I almost wish you hadn't been, but you do know me...</content>
  <content contentuid="h9618c5fegf6c8g4161g9bfdga9f1e16ab39d" version="53">Those with an icy façade hide their true selves well - but pain breaks us all in the end. What is the worst thing your love has ever done?</content>
  <content contentuid="habbf357bgf1e5g4289gbd03g762b03b8248d" version="51">Many things delight the heart, but only one makes it sing. Tell me, what does he desire more than anything?</content>
  <content contentuid="h7426243ag2239g480bga610gbcc1bf049f37" version="52">Losing his father.</content>
  <content contentuid="h36137e67g175fg409dg8ecag5440ffcb9ead" version="51">After a supper large enough to induce hibernation.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc699bf4dgb419g47c1g9058g0e8bf98d95c8" version="52">Raphael.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9147de4egb04cg456dg95c6ge031cb974dd6" version="52">Vlaakith &lt;i&gt;is &lt;/i&gt;the githyanki. I would never deign take the place of my Queen!</content>
  <content contentuid="h41239ee9g6222g4763g9f2bg6c5234eb8701" version="53">You know me too well.</content>
  <content contentuid="hfa59295bgb29fg41e5g8631gc9db470d1dd4" version="52">Fear sits in the soul of all - to tame it, we must &lt;i&gt;name&lt;/i&gt; it. Astarion - what is his deepest fear?</content>
  <content contentuid="h0635790dg012ag44degab05ga2034171c279" version="52">If I admired nobody I would travel alone. &lt;i&gt;You&lt;/i&gt; have earned my admiration. And more.</content>
  <content contentuid="he28ee85fgbbdbg4ac5gab25g4b4182a5a857" version="52">I'm not opposed to a bowl of something mysterious and rib-sticking, but I certainly don't &lt;i&gt;identify &lt;/i&gt;as one.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf576ae9cg7d64g4a59g8cebg5d21d936692d" version="53">Honestly - probably. But hopefully not any time soon. I've got a lot of living to do yet.</content>
  <content contentuid="ha83ba435gda61g4e3egbebfgbc7095c7c031" version="53">Hearing it said out loud - yes, I fear it is true. Fate seems determined to make a sacrifice of me.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8e3a201egd5f3g4197g98a2g6a429c157692" version="52">None. Her name will be lost to time.</content>
  <content contentuid="hffd5f496g067dg4a12g810dg49dcd39ac4ac" version="51">You return, &lt;i&gt;stira&lt;/i&gt; - good. Violence is like fire - it burns all those in its path. I feared you caught in the flames.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0af0f4e9g73c6g48eag85a4g647425e757f5" version="51">I would never!</content>
  <content contentuid="hcaf3df59g0c7cg4c05g8cabgfd362afb4bdd" version="51">I care only for myself.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7717e206ga2a9g4d0bg9237g638f353e8dcc" version="51">This city of stone and steel is an endless scream in nature's womb. I have felt no peace here. Until now.</content>
  <content contentuid="h541631fag35e0g48abga1c2gb729fdb3c48a" version="51">The day he made his pact.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc273cce1g662bg44abg84a0g6de1fbcc83bb" version="52">Public adoration.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8d6ae8bcg52d7g4bc8g9627gee5ed750bb2d" version="51">There is a hollowness between you, a void that your futures may come to fill with darkness.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0370040eg55f7g4ad7g84c2g028a8fbdc4e5" version="51">Many things delight the heart, but only one makes it sing. Tell me, what is her idea of a perfect day?</content>
  <content contentuid="hc87315dcgf0a0g4b44g969fg757263114957" version="54">A perfect score - I'm flattered. Have you been studying up on me every night at camp?</content>
  <content contentuid="h49eb03bcgedabg4666g98f1gab853cec3c55" version="52">Oh you're very sweet. I wouldn't say no to some gory vengeance personally, but that was an adorable answer.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6b2af806g4b33g44a7gabbfgeee60b3610b0" version="52">A fateful night. I'm not apt to forget it - or who spent it with me.</content>
  <content contentuid="h47bdc8c5g1663g46dfg97d0ge4a68b68e44b" version="52">You flatter me... but also overestimate our bond, I think. Perhaps there is another you can turn to.</content>
  <content contentuid="h109031d9g9480g4897g8c5dgae63260db50e" version="53">Good company and an even better vintage.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9b7359a5g432eg4386gb902gc1b4ce88dffc" version="52">A perfect score. It seems you know me better than I know myself.</content>
  <content contentuid="h95f6e23bgfe67g441eg8d94g4e71429fb3fd" version="53">Like I need a dryad to tell me what I feel.</content>
  <content contentuid="h744405bag2464g4e0dgb4c4g8ed894712d58" version="51">Joining up with me.</content>
  <content contentuid="h6a693b65g496dg418dg87f2g8e74c30b8694" version="52">A fair assumption. Perhaps not the truest answer of all, but still in good judgement.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7ac71cb7g486eg46d9gb022g12ab95e73680" version="53">You did pretty well there, soldier. I have to say, I'm impressed.</content>
  <content contentuid="h66dd80b3gdd7bg450egad93g09b0a9f7661d" version="52">I await with a heart full and happy - eager to begin.</content>
  <content contentuid="hfd85080bg5a26g491bgb22bg4a244b5c5016" version="51">You return, &lt;i&gt;stira.&lt;/i&gt; I pray the hearts of you and your companion are ready - for love is a fragile blossom, and we will test its resilience. ([GEN_CheckMagicPocketGold_6057ad05-9492-4630-9f0a-be548b134c54])</content>
  <content contentuid="h26f5100cg34f8g4e32gae2ega73fd2414a35" version="52">No. And if you refer to me as 'my dear' again, I will cut out your tongue.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf9481e44gef9dg4845g88bdg48cdb41b3450" version="53">Turn her back on Lolth.</content>
  <content contentuid="h570d9c07gfb96g42cagafd9gf0ba089db9cd" version="51">Our touch has been that of sunlight. But now we must look beyond - to the uncertain. To the future.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3fece403g1d4fg4078gbb2agb86552995790" version="52">Just the sound of his name makes my blood boil - probably literally. Can't stand the fucker. Ding ding.</content>
  <content contentuid="h199be8c5g68e8g484bga116ge3f3a8686fe2" version="52">Independence.</content>
  <content contentuid="h51c19931g92f7g43e2gb24bgabc7ffee3883" version="53">Indeed. You were a source of light among shadows. Still are, for that matter.</content>
  <content contentuid="h0bb08fa1g9ed5g4ba8g90a7gbbfca02d5576" version="51">Quite right. This is my fate, wrought by loyalty, entrusted to Vlaakith.</content>
  <content contentuid="hae488d18g9bfeg4e3eg82e7g5c3779a2a5cb" version="52">No thank you. Sounds as appealing as milking cottage cheese directly from a geriatric cow.</content>
  <content contentuid="h41b61224gf589g446bg9cd0g403efcbc2ac2" version="52">Gale: the learned wizard. The charming gentleman. The walking apocalypse.</content>
  <content contentuid="h61784b15g8525g4c1dg9770ga58a2c934012" version="53">At dusk. The light favours his complexion.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8091ee40g5e17g4507g9bbcg04cd163410d3" version="51">Listen. Think. When is he most comfortable?</content>
  <content contentuid="h41c7033bg84eeg461fg9f13g3a7a9b578dd6" version="52">A source of pride, true. I can think of greater feats, but that one is cherished all the same.</content>
  <content contentuid="h32b9c4b2g27d7g4695g913agcc17b3906f2a" version="52">I see you. I see the bond between you. So tender. So fragile. But do you see it for yourselves?</content>
  <content contentuid="hbcf6ad05g73a2gd487g86c7ge5fd804664fc" version="47">&lt;i&gt;Emperor, do you want to give this a try?&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="hff715febg07c6ged4agca93g490bacda26b0" version="46">&lt;i&gt;An interesting diversion... I will indulge.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="hcb67268fgc443g7722gb351g360d034c46b9" version="45">&lt;i&gt;Though it would be inadvisable for an illithid to step out of an astral portal in the middle of a crowded circus.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="he3e7a7e1g9f3cgde4bgf4e8g6e8b3246b8bf" version="46">&lt;i&gt;No. We are allies - nothing more.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="h06ff4896geb9fge7e6g0d39g9a34e90308b6" version="46">&lt;i&gt;I'm sorry, but one of your other allies would be better suited for this.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="hf97d3222ga6ffgc89dgfd13g13faf9b5da59" version="45">My lover is here... &lt;i&gt;mentally&lt;/i&gt;, but he can't show himself in public.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb892cb52ge360g554fgd5c5gfead83d4f495" version="45">Let's say my partner was an illlithid. What would you think of that?</content>
  <content contentuid="ha990cda9g50cdgc7e0g2417ge77bdc0725ce" version="45">&lt;i&gt;Can't you disguise yourself?&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="hb37494b6g4fc1gc605g914ag5c4c60d4be53" version="45">I understand,&lt;i&gt; stira&lt;/i&gt;. Do not fear; the eyes of others will be blind to us.</content>
  <content contentuid="h59c11a28g5af7gaf56g5b0ag088fc1ff7586" version="45">Love's forms are boundless. Nature cares only for the strength of a bond, not the shapes of the bonded.</content>
  <content contentuid="hcfde12b8g61ddg489bgaec6g9d2c1826b1be" version="45">&lt;i&gt;I can. But the portal would be questionable enough.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="h92279d9egaec6g6280g94a2g40123226591c" version="45">Have your beloved reach out to me. That will be enough.</content>
  <content contentuid="h28050a2egcfa6gef85g9960g4a4d1cf94fa6" version="23">Ah. &lt;i&gt;Glorious&lt;/i&gt;. Your bond is sweeter than nature's dew. I see you. &lt;i&gt;Know&lt;/i&gt; you. But do you know one another?</content>
  <content contentuid="h9ecf562fg3d8ag9f39g9d8agc822ba3dea19" version="23">I see you. I see the bond between you. So tender. So fragile. But do you see it for yourselves?</content>
  <content contentuid="hdac9409fgc755gfb12g7d45gaef15c169a05" version="44">The Emperor: a beloved adventurer, a shunned illithid.</content>
  <content contentuid="h025c3ae0g2736gdc66gfe65gb9adf89f23fa" version="30">His life is a sea of success and failure, joy and woe. Let us begin with the light. What brings him the most happiness?</content>
  <content contentuid="h0048a326ga2fegc0e2gf0f1g399f0d50b2c6" version="42">Eating brains.</content>
  <content contentuid="h76f47838g2f3fg5f15gb11cg662034b8a590" version="42">Friendly company.</content>
  <content contentuid="had72ae6bg6639g130agda0cg544e627e714f" version="42">Plotting and manipulating.</content>
  <content contentuid="h88a203adgeb9dgfa64g14c1gb1d57a6896ec" version="42">Running the Knights of the Shield.</content>
  <content contentuid="h4a3b77d1g1ec7g9fa9g7c3cgdc31680ced2b" version="42">Adventuring.</content>
  <content contentuid="h358b5331g1c92gc5a3g641dgec2508e8c750" version="41">&lt;i&gt;Consuming minds is mandatory for my survival. The process is euphoric, but it does not bring me happiness.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="hb21353ccg7d7egf90fgcdcegf9e196adabac" version="41">&lt;i&gt;My time with you has proven that to be true. It has been too long since I have enjoyed such a privilege.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="hb50bb670g0bd6ga59dg2bdagdf661e7722f6" version="41">&lt;i&gt;How little you must think of me. I do what is necessary, regardless of whether or not it brings me joy.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="hf8edc48cg47cdg7714g8b44gbe92797c8e34" version="41">&lt;i&gt;Before meeting you, that was the highlight of my illithid life. I enjoyed it... and the company of Belynne.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="h3a79ed5dg5279gc47cg55e3g9f02f8c583d7" version="41">&lt;i&gt;The highlight of my old life. I must admit, these past months have reminded me of its thrills.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="hfd92de54gf20cg97d9g23e1gd2303853332f" version="40">The Emperor's shores know well the waves of loss - what does he miss the most?</content>
  <content contentuid="ha29320eeg94bag6191g2837g6947de4f175a" version="38">Belynne Stelmane.</content>
  <content contentuid="h00d69023ga62ag0a2fg5b87gc1357527afe1" version="38">His original body.</content>
  <content contentuid="h583f7131g3e06gc6fag6b3agfbdc831bcd97" version="38">A life without fear of judgement.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf576aad7gdc5fg931cg610bg5dfafb6f6994" version="38">His mother.</content>
  <content contentuid="he998fe8cg43dcgc635gba1eg628f2d0ea4ed" version="38">Fiddlehead soup.</content>
  <content contentuid="h462b9a7fgfac4g95c8g7ba2gc641c97ff16a" version="38">Fame.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1cae71cbgb812g4676g50b2g781399c144d3" version="38">Ansur.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbfdf6b79g5ddeg8876g3c41gd7e2a7653979" version="36">&lt;i&gt;My relationship with Belynne was... complex. While I mourn her, it is best to leave those days in the past.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="h1bce098cg4575g60b5g298dge128ebba20e3" version="36">&lt;i&gt;Have you not been listening to me? I have made my appreciation of this form clear. I would never return to my old body.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="hbb20448bgcd10gaa2bgf632g82bd95e65b3a" version="36">&lt;i&gt;I am fond of my body, yet its appearance renders socialization... difficult. Others are quick to form opinions of me based on it alone.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="h6dc57c8egcd4agcee7geba4g5af6e0617b34" version="36">&lt;i&gt;I remember her love to this day. I cherish it still.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="hc8b6920ag803cg9dfdgdbcbgdcd681fbc654" version="36">&lt;i&gt;The taste... even now I recall it. I mourn its referent: a life of companionship and joy.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="hf4ec1851g80b9g7b03ge027g9ff3a55ee3d5" version="36">&lt;i&gt;I enjoyed the fame then. Now I see it for what it is: superficiality.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="h0ba0d73agf25bg42c5g56efg938c89b8822e" version="36">&lt;i&gt;Ansur... I miss the affection he offered me before my evolution. In the end, I brought him only unwarranted sorrow.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="he15b567eg2c56gede9gf5b6g21ef8a3d4a78" version="36">&lt;i&gt;This is my city. But I do not need its approval.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="hb50a2652g5d13gf210ge3f6gcb44e05da46b" version="36">&lt;i&gt;A reunion now would end as poorly as it did then. Neither he nor I should relive those final days.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="hf50d3e95g29eagda78ga573gc8d7599dbca7" version="35">A dreaded fear lurks in the oceanic depths of the Emperor's being. You must dredge for it - what is this deepest of all fears?</content>
  <content contentuid="hf8b38770g552dg54aag3827g063562b5cd1b" version="35">Death.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb864c669g83a5g44aagf03ag95a22620bedc" version="35">Running out of brains to eat.</content>
  <content contentuid="hdf80baf4g584eg672fg99eeg65db818318de" version="35">Enslavement.</content>
  <content contentuid="h4f30193age2fdg76beg5fb7gf76f1e19491d" version="35">Being alone.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7dbcf5a7g9d23g5cebg1c9cg5b41f18594ef" version="34">&lt;i&gt;As an illithid, mental chains are my weapon and my weakness. I will write my future as myself, not as a tyrant's puppet.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="hfa908116g17d1gc42eg308bg836457050b4a" version="34">&lt;i&gt;You insult me. I may be illithid, but that does not mean all I think of is food.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="hb44030ffgba5ag746dgdfecgeb76de84dbf1" version="34">&lt;i&gt;My food replenishes itself. I am not concerned with its quantity.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="h4d8ffb57ga0eag286dg2218gba461e175244" version="34">&lt;i&gt;I have lost my free will twice before. That nightmare will &lt;b&gt;not&lt;/b&gt; plague my mind again.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="h29f43008g126dg0c15g498fg0b4f861a1b85" version="34">&lt;i&gt;Yes.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="h788019d8g7803ge15dg5d77gb8d30bc252ca" version="34">&lt;i&gt;A disappointing performance. Despite our mental bond, you do not understand me.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="h3fabfa6cgdff6gfc18g9973g6db334f4f326" version="34">&lt;i&gt;You have studied me. I am... flattered. Few have known me so well.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
  <content contentuid="hd067906cgdc2bg8c3egabafg62a79a088107" version="34">&lt;i&gt;You did well. I am pleased that you would offer a mind flayer such attention.&lt;/i&gt;</content>
</contentList>